{
    "subject": "resource/Federal_judiciary_of_the_United_States",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Judicial_branch_of_the_United_States_government",
    "human_readable": "The subject of the Federal judiciary of the United States is Category:Judicial branch of the United States government.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9249375462532043,
            "question": "To which category is the Federal judiciary of the United States assigned?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8770077228546143,
            "question": "What branch of the US government does the Federal judiciary belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7794478535652161,
            "question": "What is the significance of the Judicial branch in the US government?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7709919214248657,
            "question": "What is the structure of the Federal judiciary in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5659900903701782,
            "question": "What are some key responsibilities of the Federal judiciary?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49055176973342896,
            "question": "Who are the individuals that serve on the Federal judiciary?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46172115206718445,
            "question": "What is the primary role of the Judicial branch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4340931475162506,
            "question": "Can you name another branch of the US government besides the judicial branch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4305497407913208,
            "question": "How does the Judicial branch interact with the other branches of government?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28890731930732727,
            "question": "How does the Judicial branch ensure the rule of law?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of the Federal judiciary of the United States is Category:Judicial branch of the United States government.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1767_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the Judicial branch interact with the other branches of government?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1767_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another branch of the US government besides the judicial branch?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1767_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary role of the Judicial branch?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1767_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1767_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1767_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1767_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1767_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1767_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1767_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1767_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1767_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1767_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1767_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n**Triple:** The judicial branch of a country has the power to strike down laws that it deems unconstitutional.\n\n**Documents analysis:**\n\n* The first document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1767/re-ranker-msmarco/15.txt) states that \"Judiciaries are responsible for interpreting and applying a country\u2019s laws in particular cases, and can also be invested with the power to strike down laws that it deems unconstitutional.\"\n* The second document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1767/re-ranker-msmarco/97.txt) mentions the federal judiciary of the US and states that \"The scope of the federal judicial power only extends to cases arising under the Constitution and the laws of the United States\", but does not explicitly mention the power to strike down laws.\n* The third document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1767/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt) mentions that \"The Judicial Branch is one of one of the three separate and distinct branches of the federal government\" but does not provide information about the power to strike down laws.\n* The fourth document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1767/re-ranker-msmarco/85.txt) discusses the judicial system in the US and mentions that \"Each judicial system has a number of courts of original jurisdiction, in which cases are originally filed and tried\" but does not mention the power to strike down laws.\n* The fifth document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1767/re-ranker-msmarco/43.txt) mentions that \"It allows courts to review whether a law or government action is in line with the Constitution\" and that \"If the court finds that a law or action violates the Constitution, it can declare it unconstitutional\", which implies that the judicial branch has the power to strike down laws.\n* The sixth document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1767/re-ranker-msmarco/38.txt) states that \"The Judicial Branch of the federal government interprets and reviews the laws of the nation\" but does not explicitly mention the power to strike down laws.\n\n**Conclusion:**\n\nWhile some documents provide information about the judicial branch's role in interpreting and reviewing laws, only one document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1767/re-ranker-msmarco/43.txt) explicitly mentions the power to strike down laws. Therefore, the answer is:\n\n**Response:** \n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the structure and functions of the federal judiciary in the United States, including references to the judicial branch, Supreme Court, and lower courts. This supports the statement that the subject of the Federal Judiciary of the United States is related to the Judicial Branch of the United States government."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The Federal judiciary of the United States encompasses more than just the judicial branch of government, but rather includes the entire system of federal courts.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}